Sing your own song.
Wild Rose is a music, comedy, drama film directed by Tom Harper.
A young Scottish singer, Rose-Lynn Harlan, dreams of making it as a
country artist in Nashville after being released from prison.
Rose-Lynn Harlan, played by Jessie Buckley.
Marion, played by Julie Walters.
Susannah, played by Sophie Okonedo.
Sam, played by Jamie Sives.
Alan, played by Craig Parkinson.
Lyle, played by Adam Mitchell.
Wild Rose is a 2018 musical drama film directed by Tom Harper and starring Jessie Buckley, Julie Walters, Sophie Okonedo, Jamie
Sives, Craig Parkinson, James Harkness, Janey Godley, Daisy Littlefield, Ryan Kerr, Adam Mitchell, and Nicole Kerr.
The screenplay was written by Nicole Taylor.
The film had its world premiere at the Toronto International Film Festival on 8 September 2018
and was released on 12 April 2019, by Entertainment One in the United Kingdom.
The film received positive reviews, with Buckley earning a nomination for the
BAFTA Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role for her performance.
A stage musical based on the film, received its world premiere in
March 2025 at the Royal Lyceum Theatre in Edinburgh.
The film explores themes of country music,
glasgow, scotland, nashville, tennessee.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.